http://www.asdsoftware.com/privacy/

ProductVision® OverviewAdvantages of Using ProductVision®System FeaturesProductVision® PartnersSystem RequirementsProductVision® ModulesFormula Management ModuleWorkflow ModuleProject Tracking ModuleDocument Management ModuleTesting ModuleRegulatory Compliance ModuleNutritional Labeling ModuleGuidelines & Restrictions ModuleSample Tracking Module Industries We ServePaint, Coatings & ChemicalsProductVision was specifically designed to meet the unique needs of process manufacturers. It efficiently manages input of all raw material information required for formulation and accelerates time to market.Find Out More Food & BeveragesProductVision streamlines formula management with automatic calculation of all nutrition property and costing information, providing robust and versatile formula development, costing, and laboratory analysis tools.Find Out More Personal Care & Consumer ProductsProductVision shortens and streamlines the product development process, for manufacturers of consumer products, resulting in faster time to market and increased adherence to industry labeling requirements.Find Out More About UsWhat’s NewBlogContactPrivacy PolicyHome / PrivacyPrivacy NoticeAdvanced Software Designs, Inc. and all subsidiaries and affiliates of Advanced Software Designs, Inc. (hereafter the “Company” or “ASD”), with its main offices located at 16150 Main Circle Drive, Suite 200, Chesterfield, MO 63017, are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This privacy policy will detail what information we collect and what we use it for.At ASD, we take your privacy seriously and will only use your personal information to administer your account, provide legitimate interests, and provide the products and services you have requested. ASD targets compliance with all applicable laws and regulations. If you have any questions, please feel free to reach out to support@asdsoftware.com. We encourage you to periodically review this statement as it may change at any time at our sole discretion.Information We CollectASD will collect information from visitors to our website only when specifically requesting information about our products (see Contact Us).
During the sales and evaluation process, as well as after the purchases of our products, we will collect contact information for the sole purpose of providing appropriate support of the products. We may collect provided data such as your full name, phone number, email address, company name, and billing and shipping address.
Contact information may be shared with a third-party affiliate (upon your approval) and entered into a CRM system.For support purposes only, ASD may receive, upon your approval, certain company data.
No company data is shared with any organization and is only available to authorized employers for the sole purpose of supporting and updating our products.Purposes and Use of Personal InformationYour personal information will be used specifically to facilitate communication, provide maintenance and support services, process orders, process registrations or inquiries, make improvements to our product, resolve disputes, collect fees, troubleshoot problems, carry out any activity relating to the use or support of the product, and submit notices. Further, if you are providing any data that you do not own, you hereby state and confirm that you have the express written consent of the persons whose personal information you will provide.We may use this information to respond to an email or other inquiry or request, help improve our product and our services, provide product announcements, or send updates or notices about our organization and the products we offer. We collect your email address if you communicate with us by email, as well as other information that you might supply voluntarily.Protection of Personal DataThe Company adopts and implements technical and administrative security measures for the protection of your personal data, pursuant to strict policies and internal control standards concerning the managing, processing, and safeguarding of personal data.Security PolicyASD targets appropriate measures in place to help ensure that our users’ data is protected against unauthorized access or use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction, and accidental loss. Although we make reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet. There is also some risk that thieves could find a way to thwart our security systems.Data Integrity and SecurityWe use state-of-the-art technology to keep any information you provide secure. All Company employees must abide by the Company’s Privacy Policy. Only authorized employees are permitted to have access to personally identifiable, and that access is limited to what is reasonably needed to perform an employee’s responsibilities, such as providing updates, notices, or customer service. Employees who violate our privacy policies are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.Procedures for Access, Rectification, Cancellation, and Opposition Regarding Your Personal Data and for the Revocation of ConsentYou will be entitled to exercise at any time your rights to rectify and cancel your personal data and, where appropriate, to oppose the processing of such or revoke the consent granted to us for such purposes through the Company’s established procedures, unless such an action would be unlawful.Sensitive Data PolicyIt is our policy not to request any information that, pursuant to law, falls within the definition of sensitive data, such as the following: religion, sexual orientation, and political persuasion, among others, except when you deem it important to reveal such data for a legitimate interest.The Company forbids any discrimination or the request of any data that may imply discrimination.Retention of Personal InformationUnless you expressly direct us not to or we are obligated not to by applicable law, ASD may retain your personal information for as long as two years from the date of your organization ceasing to contractually be considered a customer.
ASD may also retain and use your information as necessary to comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce agreements. Data submitted for the purposes of receiving a purchase or quote shall be retained for a reasonable amount of time by ASD. In the event of a merger or acquisition of ASD, all data will be transferred to the new entity.Subject to ChangeThis Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time by the updating of this page. Periodically, you should return and review this Privacy Policy.Comments and QuestionsPlease send your comments and questions regarding this policy to the following address:Advanced Software Designs 16150 Main Circle Drive Suite 200 Chesterfield, MO
63017ATTN: Legal Affairs. If you encounter a user that is in violation of this Privacy Policy, or if you believe a user is inappropriately using our services, please email us at support@asdsoftware.com. We will do our best to respond to all inquiries within 30 days.Request More Information About ProductVision®
Name
Company Name
Job Title
Phone
Email
Your Message
MENU Our SoftwareAdvantages of Using ProductVision®ProductVision® PartnersSystem FeaturesSystem RequirementsFormula Management ModuleWorkflow ModuleProject Tracking ModuleDocument Management ModuleTesting ModuleRegulatory Compliance ModuleNutritional Labeling ModuleGuidelines & Restrictions ModuleSample Tracking ModuleIndustries We ServePaint, Coatings & Chemicals IndustryFood & Beverages IndustryPersonal Care & Consumer Products IndustryAbout UsWhat’s NewBlogContact
